Guide to the Sir George Cranfield Berkeley Papers, 1808-1813 MS 011
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Letters from Sir John Barrow, 1808-1813, 251430
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 26; 251545 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 26; 251544; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 28; 251543 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 28; 251542 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 March 4; 251541; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 March 8; 251540 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 March 9; 251539 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 March 12; 251538 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 March 12; 251537 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 March 12; 251536 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 March 12; 251535 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 March 15; 251534 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 March 16; 251533 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 March 20; 251532 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 March 21; 251531 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 March 28; 251530 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 1; 251529 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 1; 251528 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 1; 251527 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 2; 251526 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to George C. Berkeley, 1811 April 2; 251525 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 4; 251524 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 4; 251523 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 5; 251522; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 6; 251521; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 8 (?); 251520; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 9; 251519; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 9; 251518; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 15; 251517 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 18; 251516 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 18; 251515 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 23; 251514 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 23; 251513 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 23; 251512 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 24; 251511; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 24; 251510 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 27; 251509 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 30; 251508; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 April 30; 251507; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 May 1; 251506; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 May 3; 251505 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 May 6; 251504 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 May 8; 251503 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 May 14; 251502 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 May 27; 251501 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to George C. Berkeley, 1811 May 28; 251500 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 May 29; 251499 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 May 30; 251498 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 June 7; 251497 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 June 8; 251496; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 June 10; 251495 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 June 11; 251494 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 June 13; 251493; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 June 13; 251492 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 June 15; 251491; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 June 18; 251490; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 June 25; 251489 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 June 25; 251488 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 July 1; 251487 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 July 1; 251486 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 July 3; 251485 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 July 4; 251484; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 July 6; 251483 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 August 20; 251482 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 August 23; 251481 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 August 24; 251480 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 August 26; 251479 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 August 27; 251478 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 September 3; 251477 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 September 3; 251476 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to George C. Berkeley, 1811 September 3; 251475 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 September 4; 251474 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 September 17; 251473 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 September 17; 251472 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 September 20; 251471 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 September 21; 251470 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 September 24; 251469; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 September 25; 251468; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 September 28; 251467; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 October 6; 251466; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 October 14; 251465 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 October 16; 251464 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 October 22; 251463 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 November 4; 251462 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 November 4; 251461 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 November 4; 251460 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 November 5; 251459 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 November 19; 251458 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 November 19; 251457 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 November 19; 251456 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 November 19; 251455 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 November 19; 251454 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 November 19; 251453 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 November 22; 251452 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 December 7; 251451 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to George C. Berkeley, 1811 December 11; 251450 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 December 17; 251449 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 December 18; 251448 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 December 23; 251447 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 December 23; 251446 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 December 24; 251445 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 December 31; 251444; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 December 31; 251443 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1812 January 1; 251442 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1812 May 14; 251441 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1812 May 19; 251440 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1812 May 19; 251439; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1812 May 21; 251438 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1812 May 21; 251437 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1812 May 28; 251436 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1812 May 30; 251435 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1812 June 3; 251434 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1812 June 22; 251433 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1813 January 16; 251432 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1813 January 28; 251431 (Box 2)
- Series II: Letters to John Wilson Croker, and Berkeley Order Book, 1807-1811 (3 items), 251426
  - Berkeley, Order Book, 1807 - 1809; 251429 (Box 3)
  - George C. Berkeley to John Wilson Croker, Esq., 1811 December 8; 251428; Copy (Box 3)
  - G.C.B. to John Wilson Croker, Esq., 1811 December 10; 251427; Copy (Box 3)
- Series III: Letters from Casamajor and Earl of Clarendon, 1809-1811, 251310
  - Louis Duncan Casamajor to George C. Berkeley, 1809 February 11; 251425 (Box 3)
  - Louis Duncan Casamajor to G.C.B., 1809 February 14; 251424 (Box 3)
  - Louis Duncan Casamajor to G.C.B., 1809 April 8; 251423 (Box 3)
  - Louis Duncan Casamajor to G.C.B., 1809 May 11; 251422 (Box 3)
  - Louis Duncan Casamajor to G.C.B., 1809 June 30; 251421 (Box 3)
  - Louis Duncan Casamajor to G.C.B., 1809 July 17; 251420 (Box 3)
  - Louis Duncan Casamajor to G.C.B., 1809 August 8; 251419 (Box 3)
  - Louis Duncan Casamajor to G.C.B., 1809 September 7; 251418 (Box 3)
  - Louis Duncan Casamajor to G.C.B., 1809 September 11; 251417 (Box 3)
  - Louis Duncan Casamajor to G.C.B., 1809 October 9; 251416 (Box 3)
  - Louis Duncan Casamajor to G.C.B., 1809 November 7; 251415 (Box 3)
  - Louis Duncan Casamajor to G.C.B., 1809 November 9; 251414 (Box 3)
  - Louis Duncan Casamajor to G.C.B., 1809 November 15; 251413 (Box 3)
  - Louis Duncan Casamajor to G.C.B., 1809 December 10; 251412 (Box 3)
  - John Charles Villiers, 3rd earl of Clarendon; with a copy reply from G.C.B., 1809 January 17; 251411 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 January 19; 251410 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 January 24; 251409 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 January 28; 251408 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 February 2; 251407 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 February 3; 251406 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 February 3; 251405 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 February 14; 251404 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 February 15; 251403 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 February 15; 251402 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 February 16; 251401 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 February 16; 251400 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B. with trans. encl. from C.R. Friere ro Clarendon, 1809 February 18; 251399 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B. with enc., 1809 February 24; 251398 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B. with enc., 1809 February 24; 251397 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 March 2; 251396 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 March 2; 251395 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 March 10; 251394 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 March 11; 251393 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 March 11; 251392 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 March 16; 251391 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 March 19; 251390 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 March 26; 251389 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 March 28; 251388 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 March 31; 251387 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 April 3; 251386 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 April 10; 251385 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 April 11; 251384 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 April 11; 251383 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 April 12; 251382 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 April 15; 251381 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 April 16; 251380 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 April 17; 251379 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 April 19; 251378 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 April 21; 251377 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to George C. Berkeley, 1809 April 21; 251376 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 April 23; 251375 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 April 26; 251374 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 April 27; 251373 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 April 28; 251372 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 May 7; 251371 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 May 15; 251370 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 May 15; 251369 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 May 15; 251368 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 May 15; 251367 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 May 16; 251366 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 May 16; 251365 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 May 17; 251364 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 May 21; 251363 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 May 25; 251362 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 May 27; 251361 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 May 28; 251360 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 May 29; 251359 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 June 1; 251358 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 June 1; 251357 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 June 2; 251356 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 June 9; 251355 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 June 23; 251354 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 August 9; 251353 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 August 9; 251352 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to George C. Berkeley, 1809 August 15; 251351 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 August 24; 251350 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 August 25; 251349 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 August 28; 251348 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 August 29; 251347 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 September 2; 251346 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 September 6; 251345 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 September 10; 251344 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 September 12; 251343 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 September 14; 251342 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 September 16; 251341 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 September 16; 251340 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 September 16; 251339 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 [ca. September 16]; 251338 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 September 17; 251337 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 September 17; 251336 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 September 27; 251335 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 September 28; 251334 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 September 29; 251333 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 October 2; 251332 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 October 3; 251331 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 October 9; 251330 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 October 28; 251329 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 November 7; 251328 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 November 8; 251327 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to George C. Berkeley, 1809 November 10; 251326 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 November 18; 251325 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 November 24; 251324 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 December 3; 251323 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 December 12; 251322 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 December 12; 251321 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1810 January 11; 251320 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1810 January 17; 251319 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1810 January 23; 251318 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1810 January 23; 251317 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1810 January 24; 251316 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1810 January 25; 251315 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1810 February 7; 251314 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1810 February 8; 251313 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1809 February 23; 251312 (Box 3)
  - Clarendon to G.C.B., 1810 November 13; 251311 (Box 3)
- Series IV: Letters from Croker, 1809-1813, 251206
  - John Wilson Croker to George C. Berkeley, 1809 October 9; 251309; Copy (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1809 October 21; 251308; Copy (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1809 November 11; 251307 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1809 November 28; 251306 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1809 December 2; 251305 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1809 December 16; 251304 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 January 9; 251303 (Box 4)
  - Croker to George C. Berkeley, 1810 February 3; 251302 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 February 7; 251301 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 February 15; 251300 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 February 16; 251299 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 February 16; 251298 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 February 28; 251297 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 March 14; 251296 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 March 30; 251295 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 April 13; 251294 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 May 23; 251293 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 June 14; 251292 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 June 30; 251291 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 July 2; 251290 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 July 5; 251289 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 July 5; 251288 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 July 13; 251287 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 July 16; 251286 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 July 16; 251285 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 July 16; 251284 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 July 16; 251283 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 July 16; 251282 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 July 17; 251281 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 July 17; 251280 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 July 18; 251279 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 July 19; 251278 (Box 4)
  - Croker to George C. Berkeley, 1810 July 25; 251277 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 July 31; 251276 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 July 31; 251275 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 July 31; 251274 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 August 1; 251273 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 August 1; 251272 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 August 8; 251271 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 September 8; 251270 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 September 10; 251269 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 September 11; 251268 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 September 17; 251267 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 October 2; 251266 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 October 20; 251265 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 October 20; 251264 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 October 20; 251263 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 October 22; 251262 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 October 22; 251261 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 October 22; 251260 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 October 23; 251259 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 October 24; 251258 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 November 12; 251257 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 November 13; 251256 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 November 23; 251255 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 November 24; 251254 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 December 6; 251253 (Box 4)
  - Croker to George C. Berkeley, 1810 December 14; 251252 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1810 December 22; 251251 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 January 17; 251250 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 January 17; 251249 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 January 17; 251248 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 January 30; 251247 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 March 30; 251246 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 April 6; 251245 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 April 10; 251244 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 April 24; 251243 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 April 30; 251242 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 May 6; 251241 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 May 15; 251240 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 May 16; 251239 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 May 16; 251238 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 May 21; 251237 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 May 27; 251236 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 May 30; 251235 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 July 6; 251234 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 July 11; 251233 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 July 16; 251232 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 July 16; 251231 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 July 18; 251230 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 July 18; 251229 (Box 4)
  - Croker to George C. Berkeley, 1811 July 20; 251228 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 July 23; 251227 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 July 23; 251226 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 July 23; 251225 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 July 24; 251224 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 August 1; 251223 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 August 6; 251222 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 August 8; 251221 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 August 12; 251220 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 August 13; 251219 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 August 14; 251218 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 August 19; 251217 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 October 7; 251216 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 October 7; 251215 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 November 7; 251214 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 November 26; 251213 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 December 3; 251212 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 December 3; 251211 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 December 9; 251210 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1811 December 20; 251209 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1812 May 18; 251208 (Box 4)
  - Croker to G.C.B., 1813 February 3; 251207 (Box 4)
- Series V: Letters from the Admiralty, H. Green, Earl of Mornington, Earl of Mulgrave and others, 1808-1811, 251076
  - A-?- de Dubatchervskoy to G.C.B., 1811 June 3; 251205 (Box 5)
  - Lord Edward Fitzroy to George C. Berkeley, 1809 July 6; 251204 (Box 5)
  - Fitzroy to G.C.B., 1809 September 23; 251203 (Box 5)
  - Fitzroy to G.C.B., 1809 September 23; 251202 (Box 5)
  - James Fraser to G.C.B., 1811 November 3; 251201 (Box 5)
  - John Hookham Frere to G.C.B., 1809 May 29; 251200 (Box 5)
  - Manuel Antonio de Fonseca Gouvea to G.C.B., 18-- October 28; 251199 (Box 5)
  - Great Britain, Admirality to G.C.B., 1808 December 1; 251198 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1808 December 1; 251197 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1808 December 1; 251196 (Box 4)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1808 December 15; 251195 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1808 December 16; 251194 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1809 January 25; 251193 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1809 February 2; 251192 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1809 March 28; 251191 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1809 April 5; 251190; Copy (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1809 April 13; 251189 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1809 April 19; 251188 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1809 May 11; 251187 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1809 May 13; 251186 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1809 June 12; 251185 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1809 July 18; 251184 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1809 July 26; 251183 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1809 August 5; 251182 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1809 August 7; 251181 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to George C. Berkeley, 1809 September 8; 251180 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1809 october 20; 251179 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1809 December 8; 251178 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1809 December 8; 251177 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1809 December 19; 251176 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1809 December 29; 251175 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 January 26; 251174 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 February 7; 251173 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 February 28; 251172 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 March 7; 251171 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 April 5; 251170 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 April 9; 251169 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 June 30; 251168 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 July 11; 251167 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 July 17; 251166 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 September 8; 251165 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 September 18; 251164 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 October 4; 251163 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 October 1; 251162 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 October15; 251161 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 October19; 251160 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 October20; 251159 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 November 24; 251158 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 December 22; 251157 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1810 December 29; 251156 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to George C. Berkeley, 1811 January 17; 251155 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1811 March 9; 251154 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1811 March 21; 251153 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1811 April 26; 251152 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1811 May 30; 251151 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1811 May 31; 251150 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1811 June 7; 251149 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1811 July 5; 251148 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1811 July 30; 251147 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1811 July 30; 251146 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1811 September 30; 251145 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1811 October 25; 251144 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1811 November 8; 251143 (Box 5)
  - Admiralty to G.C.B., 1811 November 8; 251142 (Box 5)